{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": " You ought ________ the movie.",
            "a": "see",
            "b": "to see",
            "c": "seeing",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "  I ________ work yesterday.",
            "a": "had not to",
            "b": "didn't had to",
            "c": "didn't have to",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " You ________ eat the whole meal.",
            "a": "must not to",
            "b": "don't have to",
            "c": "have not to",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "  Would you please ________ me that book?",
            "a": "to give",
            "b": "giving",
            "c": "give",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " You ________ more careful.",
            "a": "ought to been",
            "b": "ought to",
            "c": "ought to be",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " It ________ snow tomorrow.",
            "a": "can to",
            "b": "may",
            "c": "must",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " He ________ you with your homework.",
            "a": "can help",
            "b": "can helps",
            "c": "can to help.",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " You ________ her.",
            "a": "should to",
            "b": "should ask",
            "c": "should asking",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " The lady from Quebec ____ French.",
            "a": "   cans speak",
            "b": "   can speaks",
            "c": "   cans speaks",
            "d": "   can speak",
            "answer": "4",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": " If she has enough time, the mechanic _______ your car by tonight.",
            "a": "   can fixes",
            "b": "   cans fix",
            "c": "   can fix",
            "d": "   could fix",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "5",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}